Hey! There he is!
Good morning!
Did you hear we've got an Extendo homeroom today?
Wonder if he's going to talk about the class trip.
I'm so hyped!
Yeah, he might.
He might.
She's acting normal.
Like herself.
Why wouldn't she be?
Everything is normal.
So, that's the general schedule we're working with.
But your small groups will have some free time,
so think about what you want to do.
I'll hand out the group and room assignments later.
That was the class trip arc's cold open!
I'm so excited.
Can I move my weight up?
It's BTS!
As you know, I'm so excited.
I'm about to reach next time to move on.
And we're having a touch on TMO on TMO TAM for yourself.
I'm about to reach this left.
I know so excited.
We're having a touch on TMO s...
and your touch on .
Thank you.
心が体に追いついて 気付けば目で覆ってる
眼鏡を外してさ ちゃんと目を合わせてよ
恋は走り出しても 放課後まで待ってない
大事な言葉ほど 酸素を嫌うみたい
辞書にない私なりの言葉で 早く 早く 早く 君に伝えなきゃね
Erica 消しません
Sorry, guys. This is class rep gruntwork.
Yeah, but teamwork makes the dream work.
Girls just wanna görchunk!
Line it up!
I'm sorry for dragging you into this niche.
Don't be. Simple mindless chores kind of relax me.
You're so nice.
Unlike the other class rep who was supposed to be here,
mister, I have club activities, so I can't do the work I signed up for.
Don't become a class rep if that's your game.
Your little resume's gonna survive.
I hate how some people look like hard workers but never work hard.
The only reason they can maintain their good egg illusion
is because there's someone like me
shoveling the doggy-doo in the background.
Take a deep breath, Hone.
Maybe a funny video will help you feel better.
I don't get it.
So, any new daily life of Niche stories to share?
The clip's not over.
It's been ages since the last time I heard any updates about your situation.
You know, with Yamada.
Oh, well, what about that?
Honestly, I think...
A lot of work for two people.
Everything okay over here?
Oof, you've got to get through all those stacks by yourself.
Our class has eight people working to knock them out.
Eight people kind of sounds like overkill.
Oh, so that's why they didn't need me.
I guess.
If you're free, we could use an extra hand.
I'm at your service.
You can start by folding that stack of paper.
Roger that.
Hey, do you think the small group should be decided by lottery
or should we get to pick our own?
Won't it be more fun if we get to pick who we're with?
Maybe for most people, but not for everybody.
She's right.
If groups only have so many peeps,
not everyone will be with a buddy.
Hey, what do you think we should do?
Yeah.
Yeah, to which part?
Are you even here right now?
Weird vibe.
Are they fighting?
So, how's your class doing with the trip plans?
You got your main events.
Any of the other deets worked out?
Um, sort of.
We've already split up into groups
and each of the groups get to decide where they want to go.
Whoa, you make us look like Slacker Central.
Uh, thanks.
Nishi's getting more comfortable and talkative.
They've got a nice back and forth going.
Keep doing what you're doing, Nish.
Pretend I'm invisible, just wind in the trees.
The Pato's class is way ahead.
They're figuring out what to do on the free day.
Wow.
Already?
Oh, I need your help!
Say something!
Now is not the time to enter the dome for save me zone.
It might look like this conversation is easy,
but I can feel my pulse beating in my ears.
The weirdest part is, I think I'm happy,
but I still want to hit the fast forward button.
Ta-da!
You two work so fast, it's like time is sped up.
Well, I should run to the staff room to turn these in.
I can do it for you.
No, you just sit there forever.
Literally gun to my head, okay.
Oh, no!
Think of something.
Anything.
Hmm.
The orchestra's been sounding pretty good these days.
Sorry, what?
Question.
Technically, this is more like a favor.
When your group decides where you're going,
can you please let me know?
Huh?
What?
Should I ask him why you're what for?
No, I can't.
But I should be honest.
I want to be honest.
Once I am aware, I will inform you.
You're so polite.
Thank you, m'lady.
Hey, where'd Yamada go?
He left with some people from his class.
Well, I didn't mean to ditch you.
You didn't have to wait around for me.
You could have left with him.
I'm already way over capacity for the day.
You're shrinking.
Used up all your social points.
Yes.
Yamada!
Where you been?
I popped in to help next door.
Hmm.
I felt self-conscious all day, but she seems fine.
What's wrong with me?
Hey!
Apparently a ton of new couples show up every time there's a class trip.
What?
What's that?
People are thirsty to take advantage of the free time.
Freezing, dude.
You guys gonna do any couple stuff on the trip?
Ah!
Uh, probably, yeah.
Mayhap, simply.
Hmm?
Okay.
Why have you been acting all weird around Johnny?
Who, me?
What you mean, girl?
Super sus.
So rude!
I'm just having more brain farts than usual, that's it.
Better than body farts.
Tomorrow I'll be clever as ever!
Yeah, Tani's not buying it.
Are you for real?
Sorry.
Suzuki?
I think we should do a couple stuff.
What the heck?
Yeah!
Atta boy, Tani!
Okay.
Get it, girl.
Come on, you crazy kids.
Did it seem like Suzuki and Tani were kind of off?
Oh, were they?
Well, if they're not talking about it, I'm not going to either.
Yeah, that's fair.
Are we really walking home together like this?
I gotta pop in the store real quick.
Oh?
Okay.
Bye.
Let's see, what should I buy?
Seriously?
Hey, Azuma.
How are you doing this morning?
Morning, Kawasaki.
Did your group decide what you're going to do with your free day?
Our class hasn't even figured out what our groups are yet.
Wow, this late?
Well, thankfully we decided on a lot of stuff early on.
But getting to that point was a massive pain.
My class sucks.
They're all freaking sheeple who refuse to give an opinion.
No one talks when I ask for input.
So, anyone against getting grouped by lottery?
Alright, lottery it is.
Anywhere you want to go?
Not really.
Nah, nowhere in particular.
Is it too much to ask them for a little bit of participation?
They say literally nothing to treat me like some kind of evil dictator!
Why don't you grow a spine and have an opinion for one?
Alright, let's try to find our chill girl.
It's all gonna be okay.
Hey, do you think the small group should be decided by lottery or should we get to pick our own?
Won't it be more fun if we get to pick who we're with?
Honestly, I think the lottery system is way better.
I wrote down the wrong date, so it turns out we need to finalize the rest of the trip details right now.
I called it!
Every class has their plans sorted out except ours!
We'll start by splitting up boys and girls into groups of two or three.
Then, I don't know, merge boy groups and girl groups to make groups of five or six, whatever.
This man doesn't care.
Just two to three.
I know how this is gonna go.
What should I do?
Is there anyone left to pair up with?
Did she understand?
Hey, Teach!
Can we have a group of four, please?
Oh, that's not...
Yeah, fine.
Just like that?
Figure something out and make it work.
I don't care.
Teach is chill.
Yeah!
If you were looking for sick travel mags, I got you covered.
Whoa, we're saved!
And I'm saved for now.
That was almost insanely awkward.
Here I go again.
If I keep catastrophizing like this, I'm gonna ruin the whole trip.
Ever since high school started, I've kind of been on the outskirts of my friend group.
I like my friends, but also like being on my own every now and then.
It's easiest when it's just me or me and one friend.
Wait, am I totally antisocial?
Hey there!
Which middle school are you from?
Hey-ya!
Whoa!
I mean, it's not like I'm shy or weird around people.
But sometimes I can't help but put my guard up.
My only social safe space is messing with you.
Huh, I'm glad to be of service to you.
Something on your mind?
I was just thinking about how easy it is to talk to you.
Nothing bad.
Really?
I guess that does make sense.
At least from your point of view.
What?
You have no reason to be nervous.
Around certain people it matters what you say or how you look.
Because it can affect your status or your feelings.
But with people like me, it doesn't affect anything if you mess up.
That's why you feel safe.
Not that I know anything about how you feel or whatever.
Hey, wait.
That isn't right.
You make it sound like I don't give a crap about what you think!
I'm sorry, is that not true?
But maybe...
You know, that would explain it.
So it is true!
Oh, I don't mean the give a crap thing.
I'm anxious.
But about what?
I gotta go to work.
Right, see you later!
I wonder...
What am I afraid of?
Azuma!
Hmm?
You free Saturday?
What are you chatting about?
I asked if she's free on Saturday?
Hey, I'm free too!
Azu, we should all hang!
So, like, I have a big crush on him.
Will you promise to help me?
Sure.
Azuma, I already told you I was into him.
Did you forget?
We've gotta help her out.
That's what friends do, right?
I guess it's fine.
They are who they are.
Can't hate them for it.
They were using me, and I knew it.
But they made me feel like I had to go along with whatever they said.
Now that I think about it...
I'm a million times better off now.
I have a better idea of who I am and how I feel.
Even if I can still be kinda passive sometimes.
Why don't you grow a spy and have an opinion for once?
Kawasaki with the truth bombs.
Hey!
Azuma!
It's your buddy's cutie cutie!
Didn't expect a surprise Nabe Sato sighting on this route.
The class trip's coming up quick, so we decided it was time for big-time bestie shopping adventure!
We're all headed the same way, so we should walk together.
I never go this way.
It's like a whole new world.
Segway!
A taiyaki shop opened in front of the station.
Let's check it out!
You just ate a snack.
Aren't you full?
My taiyaki compartment is in.
If it's cool.
Can I come shopping?
Sure you can!
We're trying to hit up a drugstore.
Got any, Rex?
We were thinking of the one by the statue.
Nice.
But the one by the south entrance has a better selection.
Oh.
I want to get a travel kit with face wash and moisturizer.
Do you happen to do any good ones?
I just buy little containers and then fill them up.
Oh, thrift bags.
I'm buying the bougie hotel versions!
Huh.
I'm extra hyped for the trip because I've never seen Azuma without makeup before!
Oh, that will be exciting.
Don't get your hopes up.
I mean, it's different, but not like Mr. Hyde different, you know?
Now I'm more curious.
I'm more curious.
You know what?
Last trip, here we go!
Last trip, day one.
Hands on learning.
Wear your mittens.
Listen up.
I need everyone to head towards your chosen activity.
Looking back, I really wish I'd gone with Japanese sweets.
Isn't something you can keep better?
Japanese sweets?
Get in my belly.
Fair enough dear comrades, we'll feast in your honor.
We're not dead, you know.
It's less about eating and more about cooking.
Hey, what up Nish?
Hi, Susuki.
Hmm?
Oh, I'm FG!
Yamada's friend looks like an angel!
That weird couple Nish told me about!
Can we sit with you guys?
We can still.
It's nice to meet ya!
We're sorry to crash your party.
No sweat.
Ah!
She's so cute!
Sit down, you freak.
Well, she's unique.
Now, follow my lead.
Hmm, he's making it look like baby stuff,
but this is actually super hard.
Hmm?
What?
Tani, that looks great!
Are you cheating somehow?
I followed the directions.
Interesting strategy.
Ugh.
Does things perfectly and then nonchalantly says,
what?
I just follow the rules.
Trope as old as mine.
What's that?
Nothing.
Sorry.
Just thinking out loud.
By the way, what are you guys doing tomorrow, Nishster?
Let's see.
I think it was in that order.
Right, honey?
Hmm?
Whoa, that sounds just like our agenda!
We might be together again!
Wait a minute.
How about this place?
I thought there!
We should definitely go there!
That'll work.
Let's do it!
Displash the jeans!
That wicked little love bug.
He wanted to spend time with her.
If our paths cross, come to me for a selfie.
Oh, I'd love to!
If they stick with the miracle order, Group 7 won't get to the bath till late.
Then we should buy cards while we wait!
Sure.
I'm down for the classics.
I also brought dominoes.
Okay, little grandpa co-word.
Hey, Suzuki!
Sup!
Are you and Tani really dating?
What?
Uh, yeah, we are.
That's all things.
Maybe to us, but we're Suzuki's close friends.
It's different from the outside looking in.
We've been wondering if they were an item for a while.
No offense, though, when Suzuki hangs out with guys, it usually doesn't mean anything special.
Rudy F!
So did you have him out or did he ask you?
When did the sparks start flying?
Do you talk to each other every day?
I get it.
To them, she's an expert serving up wisdom.
Oh, to the young.
I'm starting to think you're actually 60.
How far have you gone?
Wow, they're not holding back.
When we called your names at the festival, were you in the middle of something?
Oh my god, they so were.
Is Tani even wired that way?
Ah!
We're close!
Hmm, guess we'll mind our own business.
How far have we gone?
I mean, I know what kind of milestones they're talking about, but we haven't hit a single one yet!
Group 7?
Head to the baths.
Looking at our relationship up to this point, maybe I've been pressuring him too much.
I mean, he does hold my hand every once in a while.
But if I'm being totally honest, I'd love it if he'd initiate things a little more!
No offense, but when Suzuki hangs out with guys, it usually doesn't mean anything special.
Oh my god.
Am I giving too goofy to be hot?
Oh, Suzuki.
There you are.
Oh, hi, Azu.
What's wrong?
Everything okay out here?
I'm goof-zoned.
No!
I just wish I had some dang sex appeal.
You're like as cute as it gets and you know it.
That's the problem, Azu.
Just cute isn't how I want to be thought of, especially by my boyfriend.
Fair.
But if you're worried because he's taking it slow, don't be.
You don't want to freak out and rush things.
Plus, the best part of any romance is the build-up.
Yeah, I guess so.
Still, I just want to quit being mousey and give him mouse to mouse.
A lot of mice.
You know what I wish I could do, shed the cute girl thing and pull off your sexy lady vibe.
Uh, sweet, I think.
But this vibe of mine only invites heartbreak.
She's too pure.
I gotta get out of here.
Bringing a hair dryer was a good idea.
Whoa.
Your eyebrows are total imposters.
My.
With these lustrous locks and my freshly bathed glow, I'd be so embarrassed if we ran into Tiny.
You can't hold off till morning?
Just a sneak peek.
I hope I run into him at the entrance.
I want him to see all natural, Suzuki, run out of the bath.
You're wearing a literal ton of makeup.
Don't look at us.
Shouldn't we be the embarrassed ones?
You know, it's okay to be a little shy.
Please don't mock me.
Why isn't Tiny with you?
I've got the key, so he's around here somewhere.
Hey, hey!
You might have told me you were chilling by the vending machine.
Have you noticed anything different about your lady tonight?
Yeah, my heart skipped a beat.
That's all it took!
I gotta break where I want him!
You scared me.
I thought you were someone else.
It was fear, not lust!
I feel better knowing it's just you.
Yep, just me.
Didn't you end up in a big room with a bunch of noisy dudes?
Are you holding up okay?
Thinking about it makes me laugh.
It wasn't that funny.
They were all having fun playing a card game.
You join them?
I don't know the rules, so I just watched.
Hey, that's still a solid hangout with the boys!
It's funny to think that the old you would have been turned off by the whole situation.
The game and the guy time.
Well, that's not...
Not true.
I'm a smarty.
It is true.
Spending so much time with people outside my family,
the Tani from a year ago would be shocked.
Do you prefer this, Tani?
It's not really about which is better.
Really?
Up until now, not very many things bothered me.
It's true.
That's the part of Tani I fell for in the first place.
So stoic, so consistent.
But it's different now.
Today, I have all these uncertainties,
and new worries I didn't have when I was alone.
I'm more confused, but I know a lot more than I used to,
and I'm sure there's still a lot to learn.
But that's good.
I'm glad I don't have to be ignorant anymore.
So neither Tani's better,
because they're both Tani?
Right.
And that's why.
I'm happy I met you.
Thank you.
Ah!
You!
Tani, you!
He's being so sweet and wholesome!
Meanwhile, my mind's been in the gutter
with all my selfish, earthly desires!
I'm so embarrassed!
Forgive me, Tani!
You know I love you.
Right, Yusuke?
Meo.
We do one more time!
We better head back!
Have an awesome night!
Hope the boys don't snore!
Sit her down, girl!
Do not freak out!
You know and behold, there were far more chuckles than snuggles the first night of the trip.
I wonder what'll happen tomorrow.
Don't Aberdeen deserve to be裝ies!
Oh!
Okay.
Yeah!
We'll be right back.